http://www.amazing-solutions.com/policies/privacy-policy

Subscribe & Save 15% with every order! Learn more about our new AutoShip service.
Subscribe & Save 15% with every order!
Privacy policy
When you visit Amazing-Solutions.com our system automatically notes which browser and Internet provider you used for access. We collect this navigational information to help us design our pages, so we can provide the majority of our customers with the best possible shopping experience.
We share identifiable information only with those parties entrusted with the processing of your account, the fulfillment of your order, and for providing you with information and updates about our products. We have established procedures to protect your privacy, which we vigorously uphold. Of course, this policy does not apply to information we are required to disclose by law.
We may use the information in aggregate form for internal business purposes, such as generating statistics and developing marketing plans. We will not sell or rent your personally identifiable information to third parties without your consent.
We may retain other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. Examples include data analysis firms, customer support specialists, webhosting companies, and fulfillment companies (e.g., companies that fill product orders or coordinate mailings). Such third parties may be provided with access to personally identifiable information needed to perform their functions, but they may not use such information for any other purpose.
“Cookies” are small pieces of information stored by your browser on your computer’s hard drive. Cookies do not contain any personally identifying information. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually change your browser to prevent that. A cookie lets you browse the store, put items in your shopping cart, and return hours later to continue where you left off, with the items still in the cart. Cookies help us give you a better web site, by letting us monitor what’s working and what isn’t through site traffic analysis. By using our web site, you agree that we may collect and use this information. Please be assured that accepting a cookie does not give us access to your computer or personal information under any circumstances. If you do not want to use cookies you can set your browser to refuse cookies. If you disable cookies, please call the appropriate order number, listed below, to place your order.
Security Guaranteed
We use secure socket layers (SSL), an advanced encryption technology that protects your credit card information to ensure online ordering. SSL encrypts all ordering information, including your name, address and credit card number, so no one can read it in transit. When you place an order, your credit card information is captured and stored separately from your order to further protect against unauthorized access. We use secure technology, privacy protection controls and restrictions on employee access, to safeguard your personal information. If your browser does not support SSL, or if you don’t want to send your credit card information via the web, just call the appropriate Customer Service site from the numbers below.
Remarketing
By visiting our site, third parties may place cookies on users’ browsers for targeted advertising purposes. For example, IP addresses, cookie identifiers, and website activity are collected for targeted advertising.
This data may be used by third parties to target advertising on other sites based on your online activity. Instructions on how users can opt out of receiving targeted advertising can be found at www.aboutads.info or the NAI opt-out site at networkadvertising.org/choices, or for those in Europe, the EDAA opt out site at youronlinechoices.eu.
For Customer Service:
Call: 1-800-576-7616
If you want to opt-out of receiving e-mail or want to change or modify previously provided information, or if you have any questions about this privacy statement or your dealings with this web site, send an e-mail to:
CustomerService@amazing-solutions.com
Join Our Mailing List and Get 15% OFF Your First Order
Support
Contact Us
Shipping Policy
Refund Policy
Privacy Policy
Terms of Service
All of our formulas deliver immediate and powerful results, time after time. And each one comes with a 100% money-back guarantee.
Shop Now
Privacy Policy
Terms of Service
Copyright © 2020 Amazing-Solutions.com.
Added to your cart:
Subtotal
Back to top
